(Penny:)Wow, Sheldon, I cannot believe
you made up your own game.
(Sheldon:)Oh. Research Lab is more than a game.
It's like the slogan says:
"The physics is theoretical,
but the fun is real."
(Leonard:)We must not be playing it right.
(Penny:)All right. Five.
One, two, three, four, five.
(Penny:)Oh, wow, look at that.
My Department of Defense
research grant is renewed.
Oh. Great roll.
(Sheldon:)Now you can demolish
your Soviet-style cyclotron...
(Sheldon:)...and build the large hadron collider.
(Penny:)Yay.
(Sheldon:)You're a natural at this, Penny.
(Sheldon:)And as the first beta testers,
you two have quite the edge...
(Sheldon:)...when we play with Wolowitz
and Koothrappali on Sunday.
(Leonard:)Oh, gee, Sheldon,
I don't think we can play on Sunday.
(Sheldon:)Why not?
(Leonard:)Because of the reasons
that Penny will now tell you. Penny?
(Penny:)I have to pick up my friend Justin
from the airport.
(Leonard:)There you go.
She has to pick up her friend Justin.